Guide to the Artists Space Collection of Artist Files MSS.506
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Bloise, Theresa, 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Blom, Monique, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Blonde and Beyond, 1995-2001 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Bloomston, Carrie, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Blue, Elise, 2002-2004 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Blum, Naomi, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Blumberg, June, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Blyth, Chris, 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Boardman, Andrew, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Bobrowiecki, Tom, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 70)
- Bocchino, A.J., 2000-2003 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Bock, Monica, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Bockrath, Alida, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Bogaert, Tom, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Bogle, Rhett, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Bograd, Alana, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Bohm, Tyler, 2003-2004 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Boisseau, Nadine, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Boissonnet, Philippe, 1983-1996 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Bokhour, Jeanette, 2003-2005 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Boland, Emily, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Bonessa, Nicola, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Boonstra, Petra, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Booth, Jennie, 1997-2002 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Boram-Hays, Carol, 2002-2003 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Borawski, David, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Borden, Norah, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Boresta, Pino, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- borg], [disney NASA, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Borgnet, Corine, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Borofsky, Scot, 1985-1998 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Borradaile, Danielle, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Bors, Chris, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 71)
- Borshch, Dmitry, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 72)
- Borysevicz, Mathieu, 1999-2002 (Box 5, Folder 73)
- Borzotta, Joseph, 1994-2001 (Box 63, Folder 41)
- Bos, Claudia, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 74)
- Bos, Karin, 1999-2005 (Box 5, Folder 75)
- Bosket, Thomas, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 76)
- Botelho, Ines, 2003-2005 (Box 5, Folder 77)
- Bottinelli, Eloise, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Botz, Corinne, 1997-2002 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Bouchard, Nicole Rose, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Boucher, Jay, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Bouquet, Maria E., 2004 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Bourcart, Jean-Christian, 1992-2001 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Bourgeois, Kevin, 1992-2004 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Bouse, Amy, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Boutges, Marc, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Bouthilette, Mark, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Bouton, Ligia, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Bouzon, Orestes, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Bowen, Dianne, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Bowen, Susan, 2002-2005 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Bowen, Tim, 2000-2003 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Bowlby, Astrid, 1999-2002 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Bowman, Phillip, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Bown, Dave, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Bowring, Sally, 2002-2004 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Box 1035, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Boyd, Maxi, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Boyer, Brigitte, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Boyer, Pat, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Boyer, William, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Boynton, Dusty, 1999-2000 (Box 63, Folder 42)
- Brackett, Prilla, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Bradanovic, Ivana, 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Bradley, David, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Bradley, Joe, 1997-2003 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Bradley, Monica, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Brady, Barbara, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Brafford, Richard, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Brahmst, Uli, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Brainard, Paul, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Bram, Elizabeth, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Bramson, Phyllis, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Branch, Jennifer, 1998-2002 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Brandt, Gabi, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Brassel, Maya, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Braun, Guido, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Braun, Judith, 2003-2005 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Braun, Mai, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Braverman, Ronald, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Bravo, Monika, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Bray, Karen, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 43)
- Brearey, Susan, 1994-2001 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Breemen, S. Cariya, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Breme, Jochen, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Bremer, Sebastiaan, 2004 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Brennan, Aillinn, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Brennecke, Jochen, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Brenneman Eno, Kristin, 1999-2002 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Brenner, Beryl, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Brent, Adam, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Breslow, Josh, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Brew, Jeanette, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Brewster, Jennilie, 2002-2003 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Brickajlik, Scott, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Brickner, Alice, 1991-1996 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Bridgman, Mary, 1997-2000 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Brier, Amy, 1995-2001 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Bright, Kevin, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Brinker, Robert, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Brock, M. Hovey, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Brodie, Ashley, 2002-2004 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Brodkin, Ed, 2002-2005 (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Brody, Anne, 1980-1996 (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Brody, David, 1988-2000 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Brody, David B., 1992-1996 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- Brody, Lisa, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- Brody, Michele, 1996-2003 (Box 6, Folder 68)
- Brody, Sally, 1994-2001 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- Brody-Lederman, Stephanie, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 70)
- Broersma, Virginia, 2004-2005 (Box 6, Folder 71)
- Brogan, John, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 72)
- Broit, Sharon, 1998-2003 (Box 6, Folder 73)
- Bronstein, Marcie Jan, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 74)
- Brooks, Dorothy, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 76)
- Broomer, Zenna, 1996-2005 (Box 6, Folder 75)
- Brotherton, Marc, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 77)
- Brough, Helen, 1999-2004 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Brown, Ellie, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Brown, Eric, 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 91)
- Brown, Janine, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Brown, Jodi, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Brown, Karen, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Brown, Laurie Halsey, 1997-2002 (Box 62, Folder 88)
- Brown, Linda, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Brown, Lowell, 1999-2003 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Brown, Maggi, 1992-2001 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Brown Snygg, Virginia, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Brownell, Mia, 1996-2000 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Bruce, Greg, 1997-2000 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Bruce, Richard, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Bruhn, Roger, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Brumer, Miriam, 1980-2004 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Brundage, Susan Marie, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- Bruno, Andrea, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Bruns, Carol, 1997-2001 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Bruso, Arthur, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Brunswick, Cecile, 1986-2001 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Bryant, Norman, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Brydelsky, Tom, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Bryen, Mija, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Bryers, Gisele, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 44)
- Bucalo, Domenica, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Bucalo, Domenica, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Buckbee, Craig, 1994-1997 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Buckley, Micheal, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Buckley, Naomi, 1999-2001 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Buckley, Rick, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Budash, Susan, 1998-2001 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Budzinski, Neil, 1997-2002 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Bugash, Dianne, 1992-2000 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Bull, Fran, 1992-1994 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Bulthuis, Margreet, 1998-2002 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Bum-Joo, Jeon, 2002-2004 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Bumiller, Trine, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Bunkley, Brit, 1984-2004 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Bunting, Buddy, 2001-2003 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Buraimoh, Lanre, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Burden, David James, 2000-2004 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Burgunder, Jane, 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Burke, David, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Burke, Jessyca, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Burke, Matthew, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 45)
- Burnham, Steven, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 46)
- Burton, Caroline, 2000-2003 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Burton, Mike, 1999-2002 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Burtonwood and Holmes, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Busutil, Bridget, 2003 (Box 63, Folder 47)
- Butler, Luke, 1999-2005 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Butler, Renee, 1999-2001 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Buzawa, Franz, 1993-1996 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Bykowsky, John, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Byron, Judy, 1991-2001 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Bystrom Sims, Johanna, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 50)
- Bytnerowicz, Kasia, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Byun, Jee-Hee, 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 51)
- Cadiz, Edwin, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 52)
- Cahill, Mo, 1986-2001 (Box 7, Folder 53)
- Cahill, Timothy, 1999-2002 (Box 7, Folder 54)
- Cahill, Zachary, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- Caiced, Jaimme, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 55)
- Caire, Charmaine, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 56)
- Caivano, Ernesto, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 57)
- Cal, Santiago, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 58)
- Calderwood, Jamie, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 59)
- Calfee, Liz, 2002 (Box 64, Folder 88)
- Callahan, Catherine, 1999-2002 (Box 7, Folder 60)
- Callahan, Kit, 1994-2000 (Box 7, Folder 61)
- Callinan, Matthew, 1995-2005 (Box 7, Folder 62)
- Calvert, Kenneth, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 63)
- Calvin, Jane, 1998-2005 (Box 7, Folder 64)
- Calvin, Peter, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 65)
- Cambre, Javier, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Cambre, Michael, 2002-2004 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Cameron, Louis, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Camilli, Susan, 2000-2001 (Box 63, Folder 47)
- Campbell, Ian, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Campbell, Karin, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Campbell, K L, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Campbell, Kristine, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Campbell, Laurie, 1991-1995 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Campbell, Lee, 2000-2005 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Campo SALINAS, Ignacio, 1997-2004 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Canales, Juan, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Canning, Megan, 2001-2004 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Cannizzaro, Claudia, 1998-2003 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Cannon, Jessica, 2003-2005 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Cantela, Jeffrey, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Cantiello, Abramo, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Cantor, Laura, 1993-2001 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Capaldi, Patti, 1993-2000 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Capasso, Ariadna, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Capitulo, Lorina, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Capmarty, Jean-Claude, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Capone, Lisa, 1999-2005 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Carbone, Diane, 1989-2002 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Carcamo, Karlos, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Cardelus, Maggie, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Carel, Sari, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 48)
- Carey, Tom, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Carheden, Hikan, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Carideo, Marguerite, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Carioscia, Robert, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Carla, Benedehi, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Carlin, Phyllis, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Carlin, Tova, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Carlson, Dana, 1997-2001 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Carmel, Alexandra, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Carnahan, Susan, 1997-2004 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Carner, Deric, 1998-2003 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Carossa, Arianna, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Carpenter, Chris, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Carpenter, Laurel Jay, 1999-2004 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- Carpenter, L. G., 1999 (Box 63, Folder 49)
- Carpenter, Shannon, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Carr, Diane, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Carrelli, Steven, 2000-2005 (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Carretti Shalat, Fiorella, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Carroll, Brendan, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Carter, John, 1997-2000 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Carter, Marye, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Carter, Rob, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- Cartwright, Craig, 1996-1998 (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Cartwright, Scott, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Carvajal Drapala, Pamela, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Carvey, Mark, 2002-2005 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Casbon, Linda, 2000-2003 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Case, Carolyn, 1999-2001 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Casini, David, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Cassano, Christa, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Casselman, Stanley, 1985-1989 (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Castagna, Elizabeth, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 50)
- Castaneda, Hector, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 51)
- Caswell, Janice, 2001-2005 (Box 8, Folder 57)
- Catalan, Anibal, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 58)
- Catbagan, Maureen, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 52)
- Caterino, Francis, 1993-2000 (Box 8, Folder 59)
- Catiere, Alexandra, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 60)
- Catlin, Jane, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 61)
- Cato, Eric, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 62)
- Catoni, Jorge, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 63)
- Cavagnaro, Andrea Silvia, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 64)
- Cavalieri, Joseph, 1996-1999 (Box 8, Folder 65)
- Cavat, Karina, 2000-2002 (Box 8, Folder 66)
- Cazabon, Lynn, 1996-2000 (Box 8, Folder 67)
- Ceballos, Azul, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 68)
- Cecchetti, Giovanna, 2002-2004 (Box 8, Folder 69)
- Cecere, Jennifer, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 70)
- Centeno, Vidal, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 71)
- Centofawti, Francisco, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 80)
- Cernicky, Jiri, 1998-2000 (Box 8, Folder 72)
- Chabot, Jeff, 2001-2003 (Box 8, Folder 73)
- Chacko, Bobby, 1996-2002 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Chadwick, Gregg, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Chamberlain, Rebecca, 1998-2003 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Chan, Amy, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Chan, Andrew, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Chan, Gaye, 1986-2003 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Chan, Kathryn, 1999-2003 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Chandler, Alison, 1989-2001 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Chandler, Karen, 1984-1997 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Chandler, Sadie, 1995-2002 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Chansky, Matt, 2001-2003 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Chapek, Jennifer, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Chappell, Stacie, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Charmaine, 2001-2003 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Charmaine, 2001-2003 (Box 66, Folder 48)
- Chase-Daniel, Matthew, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Chavchavadze, Sasha, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Chavez-Parker, Stacy, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Chen, Kun-Feng, 1999-2002 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Chen, Shiau-Peng, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Chen, Wei-In, 1992-1998 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Chen, Yi, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Chernick, Myrel, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Chernick, Saul, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Cherry, Lauren, 1999-2001 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Cherubini, Nicole, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Chesler, Andrew, 1991-1998 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Chesnut, Fritz, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Cheung, Julietta, 2000-2002 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Chiang, Yen-Yi, 2003-2005 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Chikawa, Hiro, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Chikushi, Yuna, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Childers, Travis, 2001-2003 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Chilf, Maria, 1994-2001 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Chlebek, Pawel, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Cho, Soyeon, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Choi, Sung-Ho, 1992-1999 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Choi, Won Jung, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Chopra, Nikhil, 2001-2003 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Chorpenning, Susan, 1990-2001 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Chow, Elaine, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 54)
- Chow, Saimon, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 53)
- Christensen, Irene, 1991-2000 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Christensen, Laura, 1999-2003 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Christenson, Susan, 1994-2000 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Christian, Kurt, 2002-2004 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Christian, Kurt, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Christiner, Hedina, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Choy, Dee-Dee, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 55)
- Chuang, Fred, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Chubar, Alexander, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Chun, Clarence, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Chun, Shan, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Chun, Sunok, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 56)
- Chung, Andrew, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Chung, Haessen, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Chung, Kang, 1999-2001 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Church, Elise, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Church, Judi, 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Church, Monica d., 2005 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- Churchill, Lauren, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Churchouse, Clare, 2002-2005 (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Chutiwongpeti, Sarawut, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 57)
- Ciancibelli, Dominic, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 57)
- Cicala, Luigi, 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 58)
- Cimino, Domenic, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- Cintron, Eduardo, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 60)
- Cirmo, Brian, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 61)
- Citrin, Ione, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Ciurej and Lochman, 1980-2004 (Box 9, Folder 63)
- Cladis, George, 1988-2001 (Box 9, Folder 64)
- Clancy, Sue, 2005 (Box 62, Folder 96)
- Clark, Claire, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 66)
- Clark, James, 1979-2000 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- Clark, Margaret, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 68)
- Clark, Zara, 2004 (Box 62, Folder 89)
- Clark and Travanti, MM, 1996 (Box 55, Folder 39)
- Clarke, Nuala, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 69)
- Clarke, Robert, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 70)
- Clarke, Susan, 1981-1994 (Box 9, Folder 71)
- Clarke-Laurence, Caroline, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 72)
- Clary, Christopher, 2001-2003 (Box 9, Folder 73)
- Clasen, Jenny, 2002 (Box 62, Folder 90)
- Clay, Lauren, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 74)
- Cleary, Donna, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 75)
- Cleasby, Dennis, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 65)
- Clifford, Cary, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 76)
- Clifford, Cary, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Clifford, Tim, 1999-2002 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Clifton, Gregg, 1990-1994 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Climaco, Cammi, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Close, Laurie, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Clovis, Donna, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Coates, Jennifer, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Cochran, Malcolm, 1991-1995 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Code, Audrey, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Coets Gilcozar, Bernard, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Coffey, Anthony, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Cogan, Orly, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 58)
- Cohen, Elizabeth, 1994-2002 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Cohen, Gary Joseph, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Cohen, Lionel, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Cohen, Lital, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Cohen, Nancy, 1997-2002 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Cohen, Samm, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Cohen, Sandra, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Cohen, Seth, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Cohen, Tamar, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Cohen, Zoe, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Cohen and Talley, 1995-2002 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Coig, Luis, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Colabucci, Rin, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Cole, Jeanette, 1991-1996 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Cole, Kenny, 1999-2003 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Cole, Michael, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Cole, Willie, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Colebrook, Ben, 1990-2005 (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Coleman, Barbara, 1996-2000 (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Coles, Gary, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Colichon, Cecy, 1997-2002 (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Collier, Brian, 2000-2003 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Collier, George, 1999-2001 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Collins, C J, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Collins, David, 2000-2001 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Collins, Hazel, 2001-2003 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Colman, Joan, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Colmer, Roy, 1990-2002 (Box 95, Folder 1)
- Colomer, Michele, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Colon Astacio, Mariestella, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Colton-Skolnick, Judith, 1993-1998 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Colvin, Anne, 2002-2004 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Colvin, Rob, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Comanescu, Nicolae, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- Commito, Gianna, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Como, Ken, 1998 (Box 63, Folder 59)
- Compton, Rob, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Concagh, James, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- Concannon, Leslie, 1998-2001 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Concepcion, Ernest, 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- Confer, Alex, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Conklin, Paul, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 60)
- Conlon, Elizabeth, 2000-2002 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Conlon, Rhys, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Connelly, Michael Patrick, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Connely, Claudia, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Conners, Gary, 2002 (Box 63, Folder 61)
- Connerton, Kim, 2001-2005 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Connet, Frank, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Conrad, Doreane, 1998-2001 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Conrad, Jillian, 2003-2005 (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Conroy, Melissa, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 59)
- Constantino, Valerie, 1999-2006 (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Contegiacomo, Thomas, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Contello, Joseph, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 62)
- Cook, Heather, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Cook-Dizney, Brett, 1994-1998 (Box 63, Folder 62)
- Cook-Schmidt, Gisela, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 63)
- Cooke, Richard, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Coon, Cheryl, 1998-2002 (Box 10, Folder 65)
- Cooney, Dan, 2000-2002 (Box 10, Folder 67)
- Coons, Katherine, 2001-2004 (Box 10, Folder 66)
- Cooper, Andrea, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 68)
- Cooper, Cynthia, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 69)
- Cooper, Lilian, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 70)
- Cooper, Marcia, 2000-2002 (Box 10, Folder 71)
- Cooper, Pam, 1992-2000 (Box 10, Folder 73)
- Copp, Mary Alice, 1997-2001 (Box 10, Folder 75)
- Coppola, Edward, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 76)
- Coppola, Jeri, 1989-1994 (Box 10, Folder 77)
- Copoulos, John, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 74)
- Corey, Claire, 1998-2001 (Box 10, Folder 78)
- Cornejo, Cesar, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 79)
- Corno, Donna, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 80)
- Corr, Will, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Correia, Margarida, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Corson, Andrea, 1997-2001 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Costa, Eileen, 1998-2001 (Box 10, Folder 72)
- Cote, Andrea, 1997-2005 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Coulson, Lisa, 2002-2004 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Counts, Karey Maurice, 1998-2000 (Box 63, Folder 64)
- Covelli, Fabrice, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 65)
- Cowell, Kelina, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Cowing, Julia, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Cowper-Smith, Melissa, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Cox, Heather, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Cox, Stephen, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Cox, Willa, 2001-2005 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Cracco, Derek, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Crafts, Lisa, 1992-2001 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Craig, Christopher, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Craig, Robert, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Crain, Damon, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Cramer, Matthew, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Craven, K., 2004 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Crawford, Mark, 2001-2003 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Crawford, Victor, 1994-1996 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Cray, Fred, 1991-1998 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Creus, Guillermo, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Creyts, Maria, 1999-2002 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Crilley Fauvell, Kate, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Cristofaro, Nicole, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Croft, Robin, 1997-2001 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Cromar, William, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 66)
- Cron, Claudia, 2001-2006 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Crow, Enid, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Crow, William, 2000-2002 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Crowell, Deborah, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Crown, Roberta, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Crowner, Sarah, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Crudo, Albert, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Crues, Alicia, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Cruz, Gary L., 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Cruz, Gary, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Cubit, Carla, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Cubit, Carla, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Cui, Fei, 2000-2002 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Cukier, Andrea, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Culbertson, Janet, 1987-2002 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Cullen, Catherine, 1989-2000 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Cummings, David, 1990-1992 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Cump, Megan, 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Cunnick, Gloria, 1994-2001 (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Cunningham, David, 2002-2004 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Curry, Michael, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Curry-Cloonan, A., undated (Box 11, Folder 47)
- Curtis, Amy Stacey, 2000-2004 (Box 11, Folder 49)
- Curtis, Lauren, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 50)
- Custodio, John, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 51)
- Cuthbert and Solzberg, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 52)
- Cutler, Darlene, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 53)
- Cutler, Rosie, 2000-2003 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- Cutrona, Richard, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 29)
- Cutter, Susan, 1985-2001 (Box 11, Folder 55)
- Czech, Joanna, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 56)
- D'Amario, Julia, 1990-1996 (Box 11, Folder 68)
- D'Amore, David, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 70)
- D'Angelo, Nicholas, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 72)
- D'Angelo, Stephen, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 73)
- D'Arrigo, Berte, 1987-2001 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- D'Entremont, Heidi, 2000-2005 (Box 12, Folder 63)
- D'Vorzon, Bernice, 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- da Fonseca, Osvaldo, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 69)
- Dacey, Paul, 1991-2001 (Box 11, Folder 57)
- Dade, Joyce, 1998-2002 (Box 11, Folder 58)
- Dadourian, Melissa, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 59)
- Dahl, Lisa, 1998-2004 (Box 11, Folder 60)
- Dahlman, Patricia, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 61)
- Dailey, Heather, 1996-2002 (Box 11, Folder 62)
- Dal Pra, Joe, 1991-2000 (Box 11, Folder 68)
- Dalbey, Patt, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 63)